so um just staying booked on that
Forefront and I do General Contracting
and I have a hot dog cart and I do a
thing called H rack kitchen which is My
Vegan Cooking demo and a way to make
vegan and healthier foods available for
the hood rats who want to eat it okay so
let's talk about let's talk about
plantbased lifestyle um I went vegan
probably I was watching what the health
I think it was what the health I forget
what it was called it was a documentary
probably about two and a half years ago
whatever couple of GLI ago and so I
immediately went um over to plant-base
but mind you I was watching Dr sa for
maybe a few years before and um just saw
him talking and I was like man he didn't
cure no AIDS he didn't do this he didn't
do that and um I just the more I started
educating myself about eating
plant-based that's what what caused me
to convert and I lost I lost weight my
skin is fresh but um in terms of um you
know my lifestyle is different like I
have more energy I'm a little bit more
alert like what were the reasons why you
you switch to um like are you a vegan
are you plant-based like what's your how
do you define consider myself more
plant-based and the reason I say that is
because all vegan food is not good for
you a lot of a lot of chemicals a lot of
words you can't pronounce and I'm the
type of person that I like to eat simple
ingredients so when I read the
ingredients on what I'm eating I like
for it to be plain and to understand
what's in the food um now I don't do any
dairy products um I don't do eggs or
anything like that I don't eat any meat
so um I guess you can say Vegan
plant-based you know in in that Spectrum
what's going on folks this is hustle
Zone and my name is Ryan Perez thank you
guys for tuning in um to today's episode
and before we used to call this the
hustle Zone but um we're we're calling
this uh this new podcast because of you
because we want to acknowledge um people
that are
within um the community or uh the
community abroad that are you know
making contributions and um you know
we've been doing this podcast for I
don't even know how many years like
we've been doing it for I think probably
three and a half years and uh you know
we're doing uh we're taking it to the
next level um as you guys know if you
haven't seen already but you know
hustles on TV on Instagram we have just
reached 12,000
followers uh the other thing too is that
you know we're at 4,000 no 14,000 follow
followers on the other account and then
we just reached 5,000 followers on
YouTube so thank you guys all for your
dedicated um uh support uh someone says
that uh video is freezing from their end
I don't understand why but hopefully
that hopefully that corrects itself um
pretty soon so says that my computer is
overloaded uh technical difficulties but
you know we're still going to carry on
just let know if the video gets any
better um hopefully uh some of the uh I
just closed some of the programs on my
computer um turning down the resolution
to to 360 cool all right so we got a we
got a guest here today and um I know T
Barb uh she was introduced to me by one
of our one of the first guests that we
had on um on hustles Lo she was actually
the first person to actually do a hustle
Zone show with us and that was uh Danny
Danny redwind uh so she's been Danny
redwin has been um a major supporter of
the hustle Zone from the early stages
when we had no
followers and um you know Danny and I
have been helping each other out in
terms of just you know with her helping
me with content Etc and then she um
introduced me to uh tarb and tarb is
like uh like she's a Powerhouse she has
all kinds of things going on uh so tarb
uh is a mother comedian entrepreneur
author radio personality a vegan Chef
who used laughter as a way to get
through life in the rough streets of
Detroit as a first generation college
graduate uh Tiffany broke the curse of
incarceration in her family and never
allowed the odds to to be her always
known for being funny and keeping a
smile she discovered standup comedy and
has blazed stages ever since her
charismatic and versatile delivery makes
her a fan favorite for sure uh sorry fan
favorite sure to crack um any crowd t-
Barb's unique delivery and diverse
perspective makes her the one to watch
um as the next big superar so uh let's
give it up for Miss tarb
so how you doing how did you like my
intro yes I loved your intro thank you
fire too kind even though I wrote
it yes uh yes you did write it and I
think it you're you're
um uh your experience has been um
amazing just watching you on Instagram
has been amazing so I know that you're
you're pretty busy so thank you so much
for for coming on to the hustle Zone
today thank you for having me I
appreciate that never too busy for the
hustle Zone we love you guys over there
awesome so we have a tradition with the
hustle Zone and we're going to get right
into it the first question that we
normally ask people is what is your
story so take me all the way back from
when you were a kid where you were
raised and tell me how you got here okay
well um my name is t Barb but uh my
birth name is Tiffany Barb so that's how
I got T Barb it's just an abbreviation
of my name um I was born and raised in
the city of Detroit and a neighborhood
called Joy Road a lot of people may know
Joy road from like rapper T Grizzly and
stuff like that but it's it's a pretty
rough area in the city um as a kid I was
very silly uh both of my parents met
fresh out of prison um so when they had
me that was like the first long period
of time that they weren't going back to
prison and they just tried their best to
raise me here in Detroit um I was a hood
rat growing up so that's why I call
myself now the retired hood rat because
I retired even though relapse is a part
of recovery
we I went to college on my own um first
year college graduate out of my family I
went to a historically black college and
university here in the United States and
a city park Orleans
Louisiana um from there I started Ed a
career in social work so I was actually
a social worker for 14 years doing
children's Protective Services Adult
Protective Services foster care and just
Child Welfare Services overall um I had
a bucket list and one of my co-workers
did comedy and they knew everybody said
I was funny and I should be a comedian
next thing you know I went to a Open Mic
um I did well and I never ever stopped
doing comedy from that point on and uh I
eventually quit my job as a social
worker with the state of Michigan um
just to pursue a comedy and
entertainment career including being a
radio host now um a author of a new book
um and just traveling the country and I
actually have my first TV comedy special
coming out on Prime video called getting
off so that's a quick synopsis quick as
quick as I can give from hood rat to
retired Hood so the the begging question
is why would you call yourself a retired
hood rat um I get that question a lot I
get that question often and I think a
lot of people um they view the word so
negatively they say why would I want to
be associated with that at all well my
answer is it's a part of embodying where
I came from and acknowledging the growth
so I know know that I was a descendant
of parents who had just got out of
prison um I was raised around mental
illness drug abuse in my neighborhood um
I started smoking weed and cigarettes
when I was 11 years old um just hanging
out in the hood most of my friends
dropped out of school and middle school
they didn't even make it through high
school and um for me to have made it
through that graduated high school uh
become a first uh generation college
graduate also obtaining an MBA traveling
the world and having a um a prominent
career in child welfare and then still
being able to stop that career to follow
my dreams of in entertainment to me I
think that little girls and boys who are
grow up in the hood and who feel like
they have no way out need to know that
you can come from this type of
background and experience this type of
trauma and things and still live your
best life and have opportunity to change
you never have to stay where you start
so that's why retire Hood right yeah you
you had mentioned that um that you
started smoking weed and smoking
cigarettes at age 11 so what would have
at during that time um if you could take
me back a little bit like what sort of
environmental factors would put you in
that situation because I know it's you
know obviously it's where you grow up
and the people people around you are
doing it but you know what what were the
the what were the
um what gave you the signal to want to
go down that path at an early
age well I think that um it's just a
product of of my environment so the way
the neighborhood I grew up in uh
children were often treated as adults
and a lot of our parents came from that
80s crack boom where we were pretty much
kind of raising ourselves now don't get
me wrong my neighborhood was like a
village so everyone on my street looked
out for each other but that still
doesn't stop the
overall Cadence of that neighborhood so
if you have adults in that neighborhood
that are glorifying weed smoking and
cigarettes smoking plus both of your
parents smoke cigarettes this is what
you see all the time you become curious
and when you don't have anybody to
directly talk to you about the ills of
those things
or make those things really what they
were which is dangerous um but
everybody's walking around looking cool
smoking cigarettes and you want to be an
adult anyway because when I was 11 years
old um it wasn't popular to be a kid and
play with dolls anymore we wanted to be
adults we had adults that made us feel
like we were adults so we adult behavior
and um it was all bad trust me but it
was just a everyday thing in my
neighborhood I wasn't the only 11 year
old smoking yeah smoking smoking when I
was 13 and all of my friends smoke
cigarettes so that's just the type of
environment and neighborhood we were
living in yeah for us and like and I
know this because like when I was 15 I
was smoking and then you know my friends
were smoking some of them were smoking
since they were 12 and whatnot and it's
usually because yeah like you're right
it's your your product of your
environment and you don't really know
better um and some kids grew up in homes
where the parents didn't really give a
damn didn't really care you know and a
lot of parents grow up thinking that um
they just want to um be their their kids
friend it's like you know what if I'm a
really good parent you know you could
talk to me about anything and I think
that's that's part of the problem uh
because the kids don't know any better
and when the kid doesn't feel like they
have structure or have like any limit
then that that's what tends to then the
kid thinks that they're adult they make
all the decisions and that's where a lot
of the problems arise so like in terms
of like parenting and whatnot how would
you describe like how you grew up with
your parents well um one thing about
with my parents uh people are also
products of their environment just like
we are so my mom was raised in foster
care and she didn't have the best
experience in foster care so what she
was doing as a parent was the best she
could without having any examples of
what a good parent should be like you
know she had been foster care since she
was two years old um and then my father
was raised in a different situation for
instance my grandfather used to pass his
white back at that time and really
didn't couldn't be around my dad like
that because didn't they weren't as
light as him and if you know this was
their son his son then they would know
that he was not actually white so you
have that type of trauma coming from
those people they're just my parents
just trying to do the best that they can
and to be honest they didn't do a bad
job at all they were just products of
what they had been through my mom um
being raised in false care being abused
the whole time she was there and then
later turning to a life of crime
because no one properly told her how to
provide for herself or to have certain
self-respect not to do certain things so
she had to learn for herself and
then same thing being a man not really
being raised with the strong male figure
they were just doing the best that they
could so they did they took me to a lot
of enrichment programs um you know I
took trumpet lessons I took dance
lessons but they still had their own add
addictions and their own afflictions
which meant that they were going to do
so good but like you say at some points
I wasn't going to be supervised I did
grow up with a limited amount of of
supervision because my mom she was like
you say let's be friends a little bit
and my dad was more of
the disciplinarian but he lost his
kidneys when I was n years old which
meant that it was a limited in what
could do so yes so I I pretty much was
but I will say this about the way I was
raised um I think sometimes when people
are too strict on their kids they turn
and do the same thing we were doing uh
without having any structure so it
really has to be a balance it does yeah
it does have to be a balance and I can
agree because um my mom was a young
young mother when she had us and you
know this you know the same narrative
single mother and you know we were three
three badass kids but the um I guess the
re the reality was is that we didn't
turn out um like my mom didn't have much
she was making minimum wage um and
didn't turn out the way that you know a
lot of kids would turn out in in some of
those environments and it's just because
like even though like my mom was working
all the time and wasn't
around we just had sense right just knew
that if if if we she CAU us doing
something bad that we would get our ass
whooped and you know what I mean and we
don't even have that kind of parenting
today but you know we kind of
knew you know we we kind of knew that um
that we would get in trouble but either
way like I guess it it but again it
takes a balance you have to be strict
with your kids but you don't want to
push too far off the edge um being so
strict that you know they want to do bad
or they want to know what that that that
life is like you know what I mean so
like like you said it does definitely
take a balance now speaking of balance
you from that you being a product of
your environment you took that and
created um you know a new pathway for
yourself and you and the stuff that
you've done has been unprecedented in
your family so you went into social work
like what what caused you to want to go
in that direction well I went in that
direction as a direct result of the way
that my mother was rais so it was kind
of me giving back um and I just wanted
to come in and be the social worker that
I felt like my mom should have had or if
she would have had maybe would not have
made certain decisions in her life that
she made um
so that's how I ended up going into
foster care um you know I was like you
know what I'm going to give back and I'm
going to help to make someone else's
life better but because the crazy part
is my mom had her own afflictions but
all of my aunties and uncles were very
successful um and able to overcome some
people had better homes than others some
of my aunts and uncles were already of
age to you know pretty much get married
and leave um so they all were extremely
successful and I saw the difference in
them having some successful stories in
foster care and my mom who had a
horrible damn near lifetime
TV movie story um in the difference that
made and I I wanted to be the change in
someone's life so um and then on top of
that I have done so much messed up stuff
as a teenager I mean you know I I was I
was truly in the hood out here in the
streets so I me I think that I can
relate to a lot of kids who are out here
and help them um you know pretty much
changed their
lives yeah and you know and what were
some of the experiences that you had um
being a um uh being in social work you
know like what what sort of things did
you do to transform some of these kids
lives I mean um it's it's been countless
things like uh you know I've spent a lot
of my own money um I do agree that in
the foster care system and here in the
state of Michigan it is grossly
underfunded and I just to give an
example when I came out of college in
2004 all the way to now 2019 one week
from 2020 they still received the same
rate per day they have never received an
increase in funding or the amount that
foster parents get in the last 15 years
so you increasing and your amount of
money that you make per year for a cost
of living increase whereas they're still
getting
$14.59 a day that's the feed
turn lights on turn lights off um so
I've spent a lot of my own money and
I've also went on my way to keep a lot
of families uh United because sometimes
foster care is not always the best
choice for some kids it actually ruins a
lot of kids lives they don't get in good
foster homes or the trauma just from
being removed from their families so um
I mean I think I've saved hundreds of
kids from actually going into foster
care by going out of my way or doing
simple things to help the parents keep
the kids in their home so um and I've
also mentored a lot of uh young youth
so and that's the thing like do you
think that you were a a little bit more
understanding um than than your peers
that were in um social work because I
know that you know there's there's a
brutal side to social work um where
there are some people that are not from
the community um that don't don't
understand the community and yet they're
making decisions that are negatively
impacting some of these kids and and I
think that even with some of the kids
that are in foster care a lot of them
don't have really positive
experiences um with with the people that
are take that have guardianship over
them know you you often hear um women
and men being abused physically sexually
um or mentally by these parents um so
when you and then you have the then you
have this the social worker that has
sometimes a
disconnect with you know what's
happening with the youth um and that
that causes the youth to even lash out
even more so from your experience do you
think that you were
more understanding did you uh did you
have more empathy when you were dealing
with the famili opposed to some of the
peers that you were working
with um absolutely absolutely absolutely
I think that people relate to things
that they understand a little better and
I think that that's why diversity is so
important because look at the media and
you see even like a black person right
being portrayed a certain way but you've
had no personal experience with a black
person you may take that as oh that's
the way it is and I agree when you have
uh social workers that are maybe more of
a privileged background they don't
understand community they don't
understand poverty then they'll come in
more of a by the book but social work is
not a by the book thing of course we
need rules and laws as guidelines we all
do but it's not something that you can
look at like a robot and say a b or c
sometimes it's a a and a half you know
if that sometimes you have to really dig
deep you know I'll give you example you
may go to a home when I was doing
children's protection services and the
complaint may be that they don't have
any food and them not having food may be
the difference between these kids having
to go on a safety plan or being able to
stay at home well I buy the food whereas
someone who's not from that background
may say oh how could they not have money
for food these kids don't need to be
here instead of seeing the human aspect
of it that hey we all mismanage we all
Mis budget and if $20 worth of noodles
and bread is the difference between this
kid not being traumatized and having to
go with a relative is all then hey I'm
going to go buy $20 worth of food and um
I tried toate others in that because I
could have been in foster care depending
on who would have called and what day
they would have came to my home and I
try and look at it as would I have been
any better being in foster care probably
not you know I probably the best
situation whether the next person
thought it was ideal or
not wow so from from foster care and
then all of a sudden you know you went
from something really serious and then
now you want to make people laugh like
what's going on T bar so you went from
hood rat to social worker now social
worker to comedian so that that that is
a completely different jump so what what
caused you to want to be a comedian I
call myself Trio
and the reason I say that is because
depending on where you get me you might
get NPR Tiffany you might get goofy ass
tip or you might get ratchet ass te-
Barb so um you know it's just all about
being well-rounded and I've always been
silly um sometimes when you going
through traumatic stuff as a kid you'll
use humor as a way to get through it so
I would always be the person making
somebody laugh and you know always
smiling no matter what I was going
through a lot of people would say well
damn how can you even you know smile but
I was always just goofy smiling and um
it was always something I wanted to do
and I really feel like it was like my
destiny and my calling believe it or not
I know if you've been listen to this
serious ass
conversation
you a Detroit or something but um I'm
just a damn fool
yeah uh one second so we just want to
acknowledge some of the people uh a
shout out to Alfredo uh thank you so
much for um for popping in we got Danny
redwine in the house again big to to
Danny um to Rachel Johnson and folks
please share this out I tell you guys
not to share all my content because I
don't want my ratchetness to to go on
everybody's timelines but you know says
uh this is uh this is one thing that you
want to share because I think that t
Barb has a remarkable story um you
really do have a remarkable story and
like every time I look on my my
Instagram because you know obviously I'm
posting stuff on hustle Zone I just see
something new tar one day you're selling
hot dogs the other day you're doing
comedy and then the other day you're
like on you you know you got like a a
comedy show which I saw the trailer for
and stuff like that and I've been
watching very closely and I'm like man
you know you a hustler and then I'm
seeing you in your studio which you are
in right now doing your your your your
um your show like how do you why are you
keeping yourself so busy like don't you
get
tired hell yeah I get tired [ __ ] I'm
tired right
now um but I think that you have to
diversify your portfolio uh you know for
The King's English and to everybody else
keep your [ __ ] going you know um that's
right important that you try to use
everything you got to make it happen
don't just think and a lot of people do
this um you may be talented in one area
but if you have a little bit of talent
in this other area I believe you should
develop everything that you're doing
because if one thing don't work the next
thing damn sure will it's like they say
keep five sources of income because if
you get laid off from your job and Uber
eat stop doing this at least you have
three other ways and that's just the way
I take um entertainment of course I'm
doing the radio show Monday through
Friday 8 am. 11 on the streets
radio.com um of course you you got to
stay in people's homes every day then I
just did the book which is Faith over
fear tells of a retired hood rap very
short 81 page book kind of talking about
some of the adversity I went through and
just using motivation as a way to keep
going with that so make sure they get
that book that's
www. tbis funny.com of course like you
said um I'm doing comedy so um just
staying booked on that Forefront and I
do General Contracting and I have a hot
dog cart and I do a thing called Hood R
kitchen which is My Vegan Cooking demo
and a way to make vegan and healthier
foods available for the HS who want to
eat it okay so let's talk about let's
talk about
plant-based lifestyle um I went vegan
probably I was watching what the health
I think it was what the health I forget
what it was called it was a documentary
probably about two and a half years ago
whatever couple of July ago and so I
immediately went um over to plant-base
but mind you I was watching Dr sa for
maybe a few years before and um just saw
him talking and I was like man he didn't
cure no AIDS he didn't do this he didn't
do that and um I just the more I started
educating myself about eating plant-base
that's what what caused me to convert
and I lost I lost weight my skin is
fresh but um in terms of um you know in
my lifestyle is different like I have
more energy I'm a little bit more alert
like what were the reasons why you you
switched
um are you a vegan are you plant-based
like what's your how do you define
consider myself more plant-based and the
reason I say that is because all vegan
food is not good for you a lot of a lot
of chemicals a lot of words you can't
pronounce and I'm the type of person
that I like to eat simple ingredients so
when I read the ingredients on what I'm
eating I like for it to be plain and to
understand what's in the food um now I
don't do any dairy products um I don't
do eggs or anything like that I don't
eat any meat so um I guess you can say
Vegan plant-based you know in in that
Spectrum I don't eat cheese um stuff
like that and what happened was I
started off as vegetarian where I was
eating cheese eggs milk butter um and
what happened was it was more of a
spiritual thing for me to be honest when
I first started so uh it was a couple
months before I started my comedy career
and it was for lint and no I'm not a
Catholic but I had a spiritual feeling
to give up something and I was told
Through My Sacrifice that I would be
exposed to some things so I did I gave
it up for 40 days and then after the 40
days was
over um I just felt like it was the
right thing to do I I like you said I
felt better I felt more refreshed and um
I just kept going and then after I
started researching um figuring out that
meat is going to cause a water crisis in
about 20150 we won't have any fresh
water as a result of the 22,000 gallons
of water it takes to make one hamburger
um after just finding out about the
antibiotics that they pump chicken with
how chickens originally were a quarter
of the size of what a chicken is now how
the antibiotics that they pump into to
chicken and beef stops you from being
receptive to antibiotics when you get
sick um and just what commercial farming
has done to the quality of the food I
just I was like yuck I'm done with that
life now I still cook meat you know for
my friends and family who wants to come
over I'm not going to push how I feel
off on others but no I don't eat that
[ __ ] well oh except for that one time on
Instagram where you were cooking some U
like crab legs and lobsters and you
didn't give your son nothing I still
cook all still cook it every day chicken
this morning I made turkey sausage and
eggs for my son I it
doesn't and and and if Danny still
listening she absolutely had that
Seafood omelet and it probably was
amazing it looked amazing because I can
yeah and you it looks like you can cook
because I saw Popeye's Chicken um
rendition when you know the chicken
craze was happening and when I saw it I
was like okay I need to find me some you
know something close and like I live in
like cow town so you know a lot of
people don't really Embrace veganism yet
so I had to like search around and
around but your food looks really good
it looks appetizing and the fact is is
that because you call like I like the
name hood rat kitchen because you're
reaching out to people that would not
necessarily want to try veganism because
you know like meat has been especially
when it comes to black people meat has
been a part of you know especially post
like you know pre not pre-s slavery but
slavery and then posts slavery we've
kind of kept certain Traditions um and a
lot of that those foods are killing us
they are killing us um and remember
those Foods were the scrap
and the only reason they were eating it
is because that's all they had to eat so
I think sometimes we take that out of
consideration it's not that they were
eating that because they thought that
that was delectable or tasty they found
the way to make some [ __ ] tasty that
everybody else thought was too
disgusting to eat or was scraps so right
basically keeping with the
tradition it's not a good tradition
let's just say that um
and it does speak to the fact that
African-Americans we can take what's bad
and make it good but sometimes we gota
let some [ __ ]
go lack of better words and um I wanted
to be on that Forefront because I'm from
Detroit I'm from Joy Rog I'm from the
hood um all of this [ __ ] that I'm doing
right now is pretty much self-taught but
if I can teach myself to do better and
eat better then I can teach some and
maybe encourage a couple people to come
over to our side because that shit's not
good for you and it was a point in time
where meat was not even a part of an
everyday American diet trust me is what
drives them to push certain products to
you so when we start right that we'll be
better for it right and now I mentioned
all the like because you're like a
superhero to me because I mean you be
doing all kinds of stuff
veganism uh Social Work comedy but the
one thing that we haven't mentioned that
you know makes you even a superhero is
that um you're a mother yes and you're a
great mother at that because I see some
of the videos with uh you and your son
um you're teaching your son how to well
it like I don't know if you're teaching
him how to Freestyle but you know you're
you're pretty much schooling
him with with some
bars but you know tell me a little bit
about motherhood and you know um and how
that has impacted your life um well I
want to say that motherhood has been a
blessing um one thing about having kids
is it's the greatest love you'll ever
experienced I don't think I can't say I
I don't think well my it's my opinion
that once you become a parent the type
of love that you experienc from your
kids unconditional love is something
that you may not ever experiencing your
life from another person um and my son
has been on the Forefront of a lot of
experiences like I go so hard and I do
so many jobs in life for my son and I
want to show him and be the example to
him that you can make any of your dreams
come true um I try to mix a little bit
of fun parenting with real parenting so
since I'm in entertainment I do think
it's important that he knows what I do
and that he's around and that he's in
the studio learning how to engineer the
radio show or learning how to work with
LED screens so he can be knowledgeable
um and he's just he's changed my life I
mean there's a lot of things I don't
feel like I would be doing I'll probably
be in jail probably be locked up so a
lot of ass whooping would have occurred
if my son wasn't around so a lot of
people ought to be thanking him for
keeping them
safe yeah my craziness down to just the
me responsible for me being free so [ __ ]
that's that V sums it up
but I try to you know everything I do I
try to mix it with being a parent I
pride myself on being a a great parent
and um giving my son the best experience
he can
have and I mean like like with my son um
I always tell him like
because I did it all I tried you know I
I tried to do it all when I was a kid I
didn't really have much guidance and I
was tell him I'm like you know I love
you and I'm I'm always encouraging him
to do the best but I say I'm a
professional kid like I did all the
stuff that you planed to do I already
got it all mapped out so if you try me
it's gonna be something but you know the
reality is is that he is definitely a
blessing and I can see that um that your
son is a blessing uh to you
you know and it's just that much more
fueled for you to achieve your goals and
it looks like you got a lot of big big
dreams and it looks like you're crushing
them along the way because I mean even
the book uh what caused you to write the
book um well the the book uh right here
I'm holding it up Faith over fear taals
of retire Hood R um I always wanted to
write a book so ever since I went and I
got out I thought that it was an amazing
story for me to go to college by my
myself and when I say by myself
literally I didn't have any parents
anyone there um a family friend drove me
to Memphis and I took a Greyhound bus
from Memphis to New Orleans Louisiana I
had never been to New Orleans before and
I always thought that that was an
amazing feat to graduate in four years
um going on your own and uh I wanted to
really encourage somebody else to do the
same thing and so it was always on my
heart to write a book and what happened
was like so many of us do I had some
friends that really knocked the idea
well friends at the time friend ofies
now but they were say your story is
nothing special about your story nobody
wants to hear your story so I never
wrote the book and then one day my
spirit said no you need to write this
and people need to hear this story so I
didn't want to write long I didn't want
this book to be for a scholar I wanted
it to be for an everyday person a person
who maybe doesn't feel like they have
all day to read to know that in 81 Pages
you can do it and um that's why I
dedicated this book to uh the Nay the
young lady who told me I would never be
an author um now I'm an author so uh you
know that that's what it was so make
sure everybody go get that book uh
www.tb barbis
funny.com trust me you want to read this
it's juicy
is it's juicy and it's motivational and
it's real everything in the book is true
it's nonfiction so cop that and I look
cute on the back see
that's yeah so yeah folks you heard it
right um go to tbis funny.com if you
want to cop that book and I I definitely
recommend you guys read it um you know
because it's just uh you know what she's
giv us today is just a Sni it on what's
actually in that book so um make sure
you check her out so we are at the end
of our um of our interview and we have
another tradition before we we we
officially end this interview and this
is the the the lightning
round lightning glasses oh [ __ ] they
came so okay so we're gonna do lightning
round questions um the first question I
want to ask you what do you prefer
texting or talking
texting okay favorite day of the week
Friday uh favorite city in the US
besides the one you live in
Miami nickname uh your parents used to
call
you baby
TI okay um last song you
downloaded find me a way by
sh okay who uh would you rather be able
to speak every language in the world or
be able to talk to
animals speak every language in the
world [ __ ] them
dogs um favorite
holiday
Halloween how long does it take for you
to get
ready two
hours Michael Jackson a prince
prince okay uh scale from 1 to 10 how
good of a driver are you 10 and a half
10 and a half um fill in the blank
Taylor Swift is
[Laughter]
why okay at what
age I can't I
can't at what age do you want to
Tire
45 45 um invisibility or super
strength
invisibility okay and is it wrong for a
vegetarian to eat animal
crackers
yes it is okay and that's it that's the
round lightning round thank you so much
T Barb for coming into the hustle Zone
um two two more questions or not two
more questions we're going to do a call
and resp response so when I say welcome
to the I need you to scream hustle Zone
as loud as you can so in one two three
welcome to the
hust thank you so
much and what did you think of the
experience on hustle Zone I enjoyed the
experience on hustle own thank you very
much for giving me this TMZ feel
I loved it and I appreciate the hustle
on all day hustle on oh we well we love
T Barb and if you guys haven't se what
how can we find you on um Instagram they
can find me on Instagram that's TB
arbore so tarb uncore and on Facebook
comedian TB a RB and you can always go
on my website which is
www. tarb
ISF
funny.com yes check her out and you guys
can also check her out because
periodically she makes it on uh hustle
Zone um if you go to our
um hustle zone or hustle Zone TV she's
featured on both of those platforms and
we're gonna continue to support tarb
because when she gets famous we want
that check
um but no but honest to God you know I'm
I'm so happy to know you thank you so
much for sharing your story um thank you
so much for the service that you that
you've done for your community in terms
of social work because we know that's a
hard game and you know thank you for
inspiring us uh with your book uh and
and folks please buy that book and thank
you so much tarb for coming on to the
show a thank you for having me hustle on
and we out appreciate you guys okay see
you later and folks
it's almost
2020 um make sure you guys follow us on
Instagram and we're going to be
launching our social media Network um
social. hustlez own.com so you'll be
able to interact um in that exclusive
Community uh we are you know trying to
ease our way off of Facebook in a lot of
these platforms and and we want to have
our own um you know we want to have our
own community so if you are interested
in wanting being part of that please
send me your email address so I can put
you into our system and we'll update you
when um when that all goes down now um
the other thing too is that we are going
to be pulling our videos and actually
putting in on our own network as well so
you'll be able to see hustle Zone TV at
hustle
zone.com um so a lot of that stuff is
going to be announced so you want to
subscribe to our newsletter send me an
email address so we can add you because
when it drops it drops so thank you guys
and thank you T-Bob for coming into the
hustle Zone we are back this is because
of you um I'm like I was supposed to do
the introduction today and I couldn't do
it um because it's still rendering and I
gotta I got to figure that out so um
thank you guys all again for all of your
support and thank you Alfredo and all
the people that had tuned in um I
appreciate you guys and we out